At the same time,
there's a lot of indicators that would
suggest, "Hey, you know, you could go
lower." Especially if you look at like
the on-chain indicators, things like the
NVRVZ score,
for example.
Uh that's a really interesting indicator
that shows you that Bitcoin normally got
bottoms out when the NVRVZ score goes
below zero, hasn't done that yet.
There's a few other metrics like that
that you could argue tell the same
thing. So, it's like there's people that
are buying Bitcoin, right? I've picked
some up. But, the point is is like
there's still a number of indicators
that haven't really
given the the all-clear, if you will.
Not that they have to. I mean, it's
always possible the market just leaves
those indicators behind.
But, the way it normally plays out is a
low in the summer, volatility dries up
into July, August, September, and then
something happens.
And it wakes everyone back up.